<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seismic Processing on Rosenkreutz Studio</title>
    <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/tags/seismic-processing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Seismic Processing on Rosenkreutz Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 05:37:52 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cainmagi.github.io/tags/seismic-processing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Jun. 05, 2018</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/notes/note20180720/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 05:37:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/notes/note20180720/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here we would like to discuss about the some papers using deep learning methods to enhance the performance of the traditional inverse problems. The application should be limited in analyzing the electromagnetic wave or acoustic signal. Some works just make the application of existing methods, some works propose fundamental theory and some works give us an inspiration of available architectures. According to the relevance, we would like to divide them into 3 groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tensorflow Inspection for FWM Curves 180602</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/projects/python_tensorfwm201806/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 13:52:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/projects/python_tensorfwm201806/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this project, we combine a deep-learning architecture with a traditional electromagnetic (EM) forward model which is differentiable. Since the model is differentiable, we could enable the gradient back propagated from the model to the deep-learning network. The following figure could be used to describe this design.
   The whole architecture of the project         Suppose we have gotten a group of response samples (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forward Model : Curves 180602</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/projects/python_fwm201806/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 12:55:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/projects/python_fwm201806/</guid>
      <description>C++ Migrated Project Introduction This is a python-c-api that wrapping the C++ forward model codes (which is supported by OpenMP) with Numpy-API. To get the C++ codes, visit the master branch:
Master
 Note that the project is still private now, thus you may do not have the authority to visit this page.  The function prototype could be described as
float64_t *resp = curves(numLayers, Rh, Rv, Zbed, Dip, TVD);  This function is used to simulate the response of the azimuthal resistivity LWD tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for AGT</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/projects/python_agt201804/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 09:42:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/projects/python_agt201804/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This project is for AGT (Advanced Geophysical Technology) and 2018 SEG (Society of Exploration Geophysicists) conference. We concentrate on the seismic raw data and use deep learning approaches to improve the performance in some special application.
Beat Tone Network The first application is for improving the FWI of Beat Tone, see here to learn the background of this application:
Reference
When the basic signal frequency increases, the effectiveness of the Beat Tone method reduces significantly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>