<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>docker on Rosenkreutz Studio</title>
    <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in docker on Rosenkreutz Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 17:29:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cainmagi.github.io/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Report for peroidically hibernation of Nvidia DGX 230 on Aug. 11, 2018</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/playground/20180811nvidiabugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 17:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/playground/20180811nvidiabugs/</guid>
      <description>Problem statement  What is it?: We assume that this problem is caused by the hibernation of the graphics cards. How does it happen?: This problem occurs periodically. Every week it would occur for about once. It is not due to some special applications, because even when there is no burden on GPU, it still happens. What does it cause?: Here are some phenomenons when the problem appears:  Cannot turn on the screen: The screen of DGX would be kept off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Linux Skills for Using NVIDIA Docker: Questions and Answers</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/playground/20180614linuxdockerqna/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 19:37:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/playground/20180614linuxdockerqna/</guid>
      <description>Instruction Here we collect some common errors caused by mistaking operations. Note that because of the limitation of the docker environment, some errors are unsolvable. When you meet such errors, it is better to delete the broken image and retrieve the backup version.
In the following parts, the questions would be categorized by different classes. Please use CTRL+F or search for your problem by checking these classes. If you meet a problem that is not discussed here, it is welcome for you to propose it in the discussion board at the bottom of this page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Linux Skills for Using NVIDIA Docker II: with VNC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/playground/20180614linuxdocker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 19:36:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/playground/20180614linuxdocker/</guid>
      <description>Instruction Before reading this article, please make sure that you have understood how to use docker (or read the prior article). Here is the prior instruction that gives you a whole imagination about docker. Some techniques (like how to save/read images or how to log in NVIDIA cloud) would not be introduced here particularly. We strongly recommend you to read this article after understanding the prior one.
Prior Instructions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Linux Skills for Using NVIDIA Docker</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/playground/20180531linuxdocker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 23:43:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/playground/20180531linuxdocker/</guid>
      <description>Instruction   This is an instruction for those who want to know and make use of NVIDIA docker. In this section we would introduce what is docker and why we choose docker. If you have already know these, you could skip this section and get to the next one.
What is docker Before we talk about docker, to be specific, we need to introduce you some concepts:
   Name Meaning     Docker A tool for managing containers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>